ergoindemand.com 2010-06-21

# Ergo In Demand - Privacy Policy

| 

| 

 LCD Monitor Arms & Mounts  
  
---|---  
  
__

| 

 Plasma LCD Mount / TV Stand  
  
| 

 Home & Office Furniture  
  
| 

 Computer Furniture  
  
| 

 School Furniture  
  
| 

Office Chairs & Seating  
  
| 

Filing & Storage  
  
| 

Boards & Easels  
  
| 

 Magazine & Literature Racks  
  
| 

 Keyboard Trays  
  
| 

 Filters  
  
| 

 Ergonomic Accessories  
  
| 

 Economy Line  
  
|   
| 

 Home > FAQ  & Policies

##  \- Learn about how keep your personal and purchase information safe and private.

|   
  
|   
  
---  
  
| 

We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

---  
How do we use your information?  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 

  * To quickly process your transactions. 

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 

  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. We may also send you emails keeping you advised of new services or products including special offers we think you might find valuable.  If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the " _How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?_ " section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.  
  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

  * We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

  * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service at 1-800-888-6024.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information at any time.  The only exception would be to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  
  
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by email or by phone. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.  Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.  

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).  

Changes to our policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on September 26th, 2007.  
Questions and feedback  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue by email at   or by phone at 1-800-888-6024.  
Online Policy Only  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
  
| | |   
---|---|---  
  
 | 

|   
---  
Customer Service| Ordering| Partner Links| Learning Center| Site Links  
|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
  |  |   |   |   
|  |  |  |   

< back to top >

© Copyright 2000 to 2010  ~  Ergo In Demand, Inc.  ~  4900 Industry Drive,  Central Point, OR 97502
